

CONTACT DETAILS

kellyjung96@gmail.com (516) 972-0004

4055 Laclede Ave. St. Louis, MO 63108

SUMMARY

An innovative software engineer with an emphasis on front-end development, growing a passion for UX design.

Experienced in executing and contributing to full-stack web development projects and always excited to learn new technologies and further develop a career in software.

Strong written and verbal communication skills.

SKILLS

React.js, TypeScript, PHP, MySQL, MEAN, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Figma, Microsoft Office, Trello

EDUCATION

Washington University in St. Louis

Bachelor of Arts

May 2018

Major in Psychology Minor in Computer Science

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Less Annoying CRM: St. Louis, MO

Jan 2019 - present

- Translate UX wireframes and mockups into responsive, interactive features, using React and CSS
- Create new web components, including a new SVG icon library, optimized for customization and future use by other members of development team for complete product redesign
- Diagnose all incoming bugs, delegate/triage solution finding, and execute full-stack solutions
- Test front-end code in multiple browsers and devices to ensure cross-platform compatibility
- Migrate legacy code to TypeScript to upgrade code base and maintain best coding practices
- Collaborate with designers to develop new styles and redesign product prototypes on Figma
- Improve MySQL structure and refactor PHP code to reduce query processing and script time
- Work in Agile-like methodology and contribute to documentation of practices and code standards

CRM Coach / Junior Software Engineer

Less Annoying CRM: St. Louis, MO

Jul 2018 - Dec 2018

- Implemented new public-facing website designs in order to enhance navigation and user experience, using PHP, JavaScript, CSS, and React
- Engaged with CRM users daily via email and phone, answering questions about the software, troubleshooting malfunctions, and gathering information to maximize customer satisfaction
- Discovered possible software flaws and collaborated with both the Support and Development Team
- Conducted consultation calls with users to customize CRM for their business needs and increase usability

Coding Fellow

Less Annoying CRM: St. Louis, MO

May 2017 - Aug 2017

- Honed programming skills in PHP and JavaScript with usage of MySQL database
- Created personal website, standard CRUD apps, and task list manager in JSON format using AJAX

Career Peer (Student Advisor Intern)

WashU Career Center: St. Louis, MO

Mar 2016 - May 2018

- Provided 1:1 mentoring on resume, cover letter, and email writing as well as interview preparation
- Led / facilitated presentations and workshops on careerbuilding skills and professional resources
- Recruited new interns by creating promotional materials, marketing, and conducting interviews